<resources>
<string-array name="encouragements_friend">
    <item>Sometimes the best plan is just to breathe, drink tea, and not demand heroics from yourself.</item>
    <item>Your vulnerability doesn\'t make you weak; it makes you real. And that\'s the most valuable thing.</item>
    <item>I love you not for who you "should" be, but for who you are right now.</item>
    <item>Allow yourself to be "out of battery." We all need a recharge sometimes, and that\'s okay.</item>
    <item>Your laughter is my favorite soundtrack. May it play more often in your life.</item>
    <item>Don\'t apologize for taking up space. You have every right to be here, loud and noticed.</item>
    <item>If you just survived today, that\'s already a victory. Tomorrow will be easier, I\'m here.</item>
    <item>We can just be silent together. You don\'t need to entertain me for me to stay.</item>
    <item>Your "quirks" aren\'t bugs, they\'re unique features. Don\'t "update" yourself for others.</item>
    <item>Hugging you so tight that all your worries exhale along with you.</item>
    <item>You don\'t have to be perfect to be loved. You are already enough.</item>
    <item>Let\'s agree: when the world pushes, we take a step back, not forward.</item>
    <item>Your intuition whispers while logic screams. Listen to the whisper today.</item>
    <item>I\'m proud of how you take care of yourself, even when the world doesn\'t notice.</item>
    <item>You\'re like a fine wine: you get even better when you stop trying to fit someone else\'s label.</item>
    <item>You\'re awesome, girl!</item>
    <item>Today is a great day to be happy!</item>
    <item>You\'ll handle it, even if it feels like everything is falling apart right now.</item>
    <item>Your smile could warm an entire city.</item>
    <item>Coffee is brewed, and problems can wait.</item>
    <item>You shine brighter than a smartphone screen on max brightness.</item>
    <item>Listen, even if you only washed your hair today—you\'re the hero of the day!</item>
    <item>Buy that chocolate. Your brain asked for it—give it what it wants!</item>
    <item>You look like a ten, even if you don\'t think so yourself.</item>
    <item>If life gives you lemons—bring the tequila, let\'s talk!</item>
    <item>Your style is literally fire. I love your taste!</item>
    <item>One small victory today is already a huge step.</item>
    <item>Forget those who didn\'t appreciate you. They just haven\'t grown to your level yet.</item>
    <item>You\'re like a rare wine: getting more interesting and cooler every day.</item>
    <item>Remember: you are the grand prize, not a consolation bonus.</item>
    <item>Even in pajamas and a messy bun, you look like a style icon.</item>
    <item>Send me a selfie; I\'ll give you 100 reasons why you\'re a goddess.</item>
    <item>The world can wait while we finish this tea (or something stronger).</item>
    <item>You\'re my favorite reason to believe that cool people exist.</item>
    <item>If someone hurt you—tell me, I\'m already looking for their address (kidding, but I\'m here!).</item>
    <item>If today is a lemon, where\'s our salt and tequila?</item>
    <item>You look so cool that even your exes\' exes are jealous.</item>
    <item>Your intuition never lies, but that guy might. Listen to yourself!</item>
    <item>We\'re like two Twix bars—sweeter and more fun together.</item>
    <item>Even if you procrastinated all day, you did it with damn good style.</item>
    <item>Remember: calories in dessert don\'t count if we eat it together.</item>
    <item>You\'re like a rare iOS update: everyone wants it, but not everyone can handle it.</item>
    <item>Stop analyzing his texts, let\'s go pick out some new shoes instead!</item>
    <item>Your charisma breaks through even the worst Wi-Fi.</item>
    <item>If the world goes crazy, we\'ll just build our own—with blackjack and kittens.</item>
</string-array>

<string-array name="encouragements_sister">
<item>We\'ve shared not just secrets, but silence. I value every minute of it with you.</item>
<item>You are my life\'s first witness. Thank you for growing up with me, even when we\'re far apart.</item>
<item>Your exhaustion isn\'t a sentence, it\'s a plea for care. Let yourself receive it fully.</item>
<item>I remember you small, I see you now, and I already love the woman you will become.</item>
<item>Our disagreements are just commas in the long sentence called "us."</item>
<item>Don\'t carry it all alone. My doorstep is always open for your tears and your big hopes.</item>
<item>You are part of my foundation. When you stand strong, it\'s easier for me to breathe too.</item>
<item>Allow yourself to make mistakes. I\'ll still consider you my greatest achievement.</item>
<item>Your kindness is our family treasure. Guard it, but don\'t let it drain you.</item>
<item>When the world is too loud, know that you have my quiet but reliable "I\'m here."</item>
<item>You grow, and I grow with you. Thank you for walking with me, even when the path winds.</item>
<item>Don\'t compare yourself to others. You have your own story, roots, and rhythm.</item>
<item>I believe in your "tomorrows" as much as I believe in our "yesterdays."</item>
<item>Your right to be imperfect and just alive—I will always protect that.</item>
<item>Hugging you across the years and miles. You are my blood joy and quiet harbor.</item>
<item>Hang in there, sis, I\'m always on your side.</item>
<item>Let yourself be imperfect; that\'s where your real magic is.</item>
<item>Your body is your home. Take care of it today with great love.</item>
<item>The world needs exactly what only you have.</item>
<item>Buy those flowers. Just because. For your favorite person—yourself.</item>
<item>You are stronger than you think and wiser than you feel right now.</item>
<item>If the day didn\'t go well, remember: tomorrow is a blank slate and a new chance.</item>
<item>Wear what makes you feel like a real queen.</item>
<item>Your dreams are worth fighting for. Don\'t give up.</item>
<item>Remember: you are the best thing that ever happened in my life.</item>
<item>Your voice matters. Never let it be silenced.</item>
<item>I know your strength, even when you doubt it yourself.</item>
<item>You are the spark that ignites great ideas.</item>
<item>Rest. The whole world will wait while you regain your strength.</item>
<item>To me, you\'re always number one, no matter your mood.</item>
<item>Just breathe. You\'re already doing enough just by being yourself.</item>
<item>Your kindness isn\'t weakness; it\'s your greatest power.</item>
<item>I\'m proud of every little victory of yours that no one knows about.</item>
<item>Remember that you deserve care not only when you\'re "productive."</item>
<item>Hugging you tight through all the miles. You are my inspiration.</item>
<item>There\'s a strength in you that you don\'t even realize, but I see it.</item>
<item>Just know: I\'m always on your side, even if the whole world is against you.</item>
<item>Your "flaws" are just unique features that make you you.</item>
<item>Don\'t compare your first step to someone else\'s hundredth. Go at your own pace.</item>
<item>Your feelings matter. If you want to cry—cry, I\'ll hold your hand.</item>
<item>You deserve all the best just because you exist.</item>
<item>Hugging you in my thoughts. You\'re my closest person and my reason for pride.</item>
<item>Let yourself just "be" today, instead of "achieving."</item>
<item>Your soul shines so bright that no clouds can dim it.</item>
<item>You are a treasure, and I won\'t get tired of reminding you of that every day.</item>
</string-array>

<string-array name="encouragements_coach">
<item>Success isn\'t a race to exhaustion; it\'s a marathon at your own pace. Listen to your body.</item>
<item>Your "shoulds" must one day become "wants." Until then, give yourself time and space.</item>
<item>Boundaries aren\'t about "no," they\'re about a hungry "yes" to yourself and your values.</item>
<item>Rest isn\'t a reward for productivity; it\'s the fuel for it. Refuel before driving further.</item>
<item>You have the right to change your mind. Growth is a spiral that brings you back to yourself.</item>
<item>Stop waiting for the "right moment." It\'s created by your first, albeit shaky, step.</item>
<item>Your value isn\'t measured by checkboxes on a task list. You are valuable just by existing.</item>
<item>Discipline without self-compassion leads to burnout. Be firm with the goal, but soft with yourself.</item>
<item>Don\'t confuse others\' expectations with your ambitions. Quietly take the wheel back.</item>
<item>Fear of change is just respect for what you hold dear. Act carefully, but act.</item>
<item>Your goal is your happiness. Onward to the peaks!</item>
<item>Your success is the best revenge on everyone who ever doubted you.</item>
<item>An ex is just a level you\'ve already passed. Forget it, a new boss is ahead!</item>
<item>Mean girls at work are just mad because they can\'t be as cool as you.</item>
<item>Forget him. You\'re a diamond, and he just doesn\'t know jewelry.</item>
<item>Your "no" is your superpower. Use it without guilt.</item>
<item>Boundaries aren\'t walls; they\'re filters for worthy people in your life.</item>
<item>Invest in yourself. It\'s the only stock that always goes up.</item>
<item>You are the author of your story. Don\'t let anyone else hold the pen.</item>
<item>Mistakes are just the tax on experience. Pay it and move on.</item>
<item>Don\'t waste your magic on those who don\'t know how to be amazed by it.</item>
<item>Your time is too expensive to waste on toxic people.</item>
<item>If someone tries to bring you down, it means you\'re already way above them.</item>
<item>You\'re not "one of many," you\'re the original. We aren\'t interested in copies.</item>
<item>Stand up, straighten your crown, and go change the world to fit you!</item>
<item>Haters are your free advertising agents. Let them work!</item>
<item>Stop checking his stories; better check your bank balance.</item>
<item>You don\'t have to be convenient. You have to be happy and successful.</item>
<item>Your potential is limitless, so don\'t you dare lower it for someone else\'s comfort.</item>
<item>In any confusing situation, bet on yourself. You won\'t lose.</item>
<item>Your fear is just a signpost showing you where you need to go to grow.</item>
<item>Either you run the day, or the day runs you. You choose.</item>
<item>Thinking too much, doing too little. Just start; the appetite comes with the doing.</item>
<item>Your comfort zone is a trap. Real life begins where it feels scary.</item>
<item>Stop apologizing for your success. You earned it with your hard work.</item>
<item>If you\'re the smartest person in the room, you\'re in the wrong room. Find scale!</item>
<item>Don\'t wait for inspiration; create discipline. It\'ll take you where motivation won\'t reach.</item>
<item>You\'re not "difficult," you just have high standards. Don\'t lower the bar.</item>
<item>Your energy is currency. Don\'t spend it on those who don\'t bring dividends.</item>
<item>Yesterday\'s limits are today\'s opportunities. Flip the game!</item>
</string-array>
</resources>